mygenius.com 2008-06-21

# Privacy Policy

MyGenius holds privacy in high regard and its privacy policy is based on the following principles:  
  
  1. You must be 18 years old or over to use and/or join MyGenius.

  2. In order to maximise the value of the MyGenius online community, users are requested to provide information about themselves. In fact, the more information that one supplies about oneself, the more likely one is to benefit from connections of people, ideas and opportunities. Having said that, MyGenius makes every effort to ensure your information is protected. However, this must be understood within the nature of the internet which is susceptible to hacks, viruses and other forms of security breaches.

  3. MyGenius provides you with the ability to edit your profile (and all your personal information) at any point by going to your personal My Profile Edit page on the website.

  4. MyGenius does not provide your information to any company other than if on registration you specifically mentioned that you were introduced to MyGenius by one of MyGenius’ marketing partners. In this situation, only that marketing partner could at some point in the future contact you by email and this communication would be limited to products and services offered by that marketing partner. MyGenius takes the view that as an existing client of that marketing partner (by virtue of having been introduced to MyGenius through their in-store promotion), you could benefit from such communication.

  5. Personal information you choose to display in your profile, or anywhere else on the website, will be publicly displayed and viewable by other MyGenius members. Select information can be prevented from being publicly displayed, without deleting it, by checking your personal settings under My Notification Settings within your My Account.
  6. MyGenius provides a wide variety of opportunities to engage with other members of the MyGenius community, including blogs, clubs and personal networks. At any point members can choose to withdraw from any of these personal interactions. Furthermore, while at registration, members agree to receive newsletters from MyGenius, members have the opportunity of changing this preference and opting out of such communication by going to My Notification Settings within your My Account.

  7. MyGenius makes use of cookies to keep track of member preferences in order to make sure that content specific to a particular members is in fact delivered to that member and for other purposes that make MyGenius more efficient and user friendly.

  8. Individuals may choose at any point to withdraw their information from the website by going to My Profile Edit and removing part or all information.

  9. By contributing to regular polls on the MyGenius website, members are freely giving an expression of their views. While MyGenius may report the statistical results of these polls to outside interested parties. MyGenius will not release personal identifiable information of the contributing member.

  10. MyGenius may contain links to other websites not under its control and is therefore not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

  11. Any comments regarding personal information can be sent to [info@mygenius.com](mailto:info@mygenius.com)
